export default {
  id: 'katakana_alphabet',
  name: '카타카나 (문자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: 'a', answer: ['ア'] },
    { question: 'i', answer: ['イ'] },
    { question: 'u', answer: ['ウ'] },
    { question: 'e', answer: ['エ'] },
    { question: 'o', answer: ['オ'] },
    { question: 'ka', answer: ['カ'] },
    { question: 'ki', answer: ['キ'] },
    { question: 'ku', answer: ['ク'] },
    { question: 'ke', answer: ['ケ'] },
    { question: 'ko', answer: ['コ'] },
    { question: 'sa', answer: ['サ'] },
    { question: 'shi', answer: ['シ'] },
    { question: 'su', answer: ['ス'] },
    { question: 'se', answer: ['セ'] },
    { question: 'so', answer: ['ソ'] },
    { question: 'ta', answer: ['タ'] },
    { question: 'chi', answer: ['チ'] },
    { question: 'tsu', answer: ['ツ'] },
    { question: 'te', answer: ['テ'] },
    { question: 'to', answer: ['ト'] },
    { question: 'na', answer: ['ナ'] },
    { question: 'ni', answer: ['ニ'] },
    { question: 'nu', answer: ['ヌ'] },
    { question: 'ne', answer: ['ネ'] },
    { question: 'no', answer: ['ノ'] },
    { question: 'ha', answer: ['ハ'] },
    { question: 'hi', answer: ['ヒ'] },
    { question: 'fu', answer: ['フ'] },
    { question: 'he', answer: ['ヘ'] },
    { question: 'ho', answer: ['ホ'] },
    { question: 'ma', answer: ['マ'] },
    { question: 'mi', answer: ['ミ'] },
    { question: 'mu', answer: ['ム'] },
    { question: 'me', answer: ['メ'] },
    { question: 'mo', answer: ['モ'] },
    { question: 'ya', answer: ['ヤ'] },
    { question: 'yu', answer: ['ユ'] },
    { question: 'yo', answer: ['ヨ'] },
    { question: 'ra', answer: ['ラ'] },
    { question: 'ri', answer: ['リ'] },
    { question: 'ru', answer: ['ル'] },
    { question: 're', answer: ['レ'] },
    { question: 'ro', answer: ['ロ'] },
    { question: 'wa', answer: ['ワ'] },
    { question: 'wo', answer: ['ヲ'] },
    { question: 'n', answer: ['ン'] },
    { question: 'ga', answer: ['ガ'] },
    { question: 'gi', answer: ['ギ'] },
    { question: 'gu', answer: ['グ'] },
    { question: 'ge', answer: ['ゲ'] },
    { question: 'go', answer: ['ゴ'] },
    { question: 'za', answer: ['ザ'] },
    { question: 'ji', answer: ['ジ'] },
    { question: 'zu', answer: ['ズ'] },
    { question: 'ze', answer: ['ゼ'] },
    { question: 'zo', answer: ['ゾ'] },
    { question: 'da', answer: ['ダ'] },
    { question: 'ji', answer: ['ヂ'] },
    { question: 'zu', answer: ['ヅ'] },
    { question: 'de', answer: ['デ'] },
    { question: 'do', answer: ['ド'] },
    { question: 'ba', answer: ['バ'] },
    { question: 'bi', answer: ['ビ'] },
    { question: 'bu', answer: ['ブ'] },
    { question: 'be', answer: ['ベ'] },
    { question: 'bo', answer: ['ボ'] },
    { question: 'pa', answer: ['パ'] },
    { question: 'pi', answer: ['ピ'] },
    { question: 'pu', answer: ['プ'] },
    { question: 'pe', answer: ['ペ'] },
    { question: 'po', answer: ['ポ'] },
    { question: 'ye', answer: ['イェ'] },
    { question: 'wha', answer: ['ウァ'] },
    { question: 'whi', answer: ['ウィ'] },
    { question: 'whe', answer: ['ウェ'] },
    { question: 'who', answer: ['ウォ'] },
    { question: 'va', answer: ['ヴァ'] },
    { question: 'vi', answer: ['ヴィ'] },
    { question: 'vu', answer: ['ヴ'] },
    { question: 've', answer: ['ヴェ'] },
    { question: 'vo', answer: ['ヴォ'] },
    { question: 'vyu', answer: ['ヴュ'] },
    { question: 'qa', answer: ['クァ'] },
    { question: 'qi', answer: ['クィ'] },
    { question: 'qwu', answer: ['クゥ'] },
    { question: 'qe', answer: ['クェ'] },
    { question: 'qo', answer: ['クォ'] },
    { question: 'gwa', answer: ['グァ'] },
    { question: 'gwi', answer: ['グィ'] },
    { question: 'gwu', answer: ['グゥ'] },
    { question: 'gwe', answer: ['グェ'] },
    { question: 'gwo', answer: ['グォ'] },
    { question: 'cha', answer: ['チャ'] },
    { question: 'cyi', answer: ['チィ'] },
    { question: 'chu', answer: ['チュ'] },
    { question: 'che', answer: ['チェ'] },
    { question: 'cho', answer: ['チョ'] },
    { question: 'dya', answer: ['ヂャ'] },
    { question: 'dyi', answer: ['ヂィ'] },
    { question: 'dyu', answer: ['ヂュ'] },
    { question: 'dye', answer: ['ヂェ'] },
    { question: 'dyo', answer: ['ヂョ'] },
    { question: 'tha', answer: ['テャ'] },
    { question: 'thi', answer: ['ティ'] },
    { question: 'thu', answer: ['テュ'] },
    { question: 'the', answer: ['テェ'] },
    { question: 'tho', answer: ['テョ'] },
    { question: 'dha', answer: ['デャ'] },
    { question: 'dhi', answer: ['ディ'] },
    { question: 'dhu', answer: ['デュ'] },
    { question: 'dhe', answer: ['デェ'] },
    { question: 'dho', answer: ['デョ'] },
    { question: 'tsa', answer: ['ツァ'] },
    { question: 'tsi', answer: ['ツィ'] },
    { question: 'tse', answer: ['ツェ'] },
    { question: 'tso', answer: ['ツォ'] },
    { question: 'twu', answer: ['トゥ'] },
    { question: 'dwu', answer: ['ドゥ'] },
    { question: 'fa', answer: ['ファ'] },
    { question: 'fi', answer: ['フィ'] },
    { question: 'fe', answer: ['フェ'] },
    { question: 'fo', answer: ['フォ'] },
    { question: 'fya', answer: ['フャ'] },
    { question: 'fyu', answer: ['フュ'] },
    { question: 'fyo', answer: ['フョ'] }
  ]
}
